

# Md. Rohul Amin

## Software Engineer

- Sha 66/3, Shadhinata Sarani, North Badda, Gulshan, Dhaka, Bangladesh ## 05 Jan 1996
- Bangladeshi @ Unmarried in radipu ♠ radipu ♠ radipu ♠ radipu.me ♠ radipu
  ♠ radipu

## **CAREER OBJECTIVES**

I am experienced in leadership and both front-end and back-end programming languages. Now, I am looking for establishing my career as a .NET developer and team lead. I am a quick learner and willing to learn new technologies to upgrade myself with time. I am working with .NET technology since 2018.

## **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

Aug 2022 – present

#### **Gulf State Software**

Dhaka, Bangladesh Softwai

Software Developer 🛮

- Working in Warehouse Management System.
- Adding new features and debugging.
- Technologies: C# ASP.NET, JSON, Azure DevOps, MSSQL Server, Angular

Jan 2022 - Jul 2022

#### CureTech Ltd

Dhaka, Bangladesh

Software Engineer 🗷

- Developed web applications.
- Worked on the Engineering part for different projects.
- · Lead a team.
- Technologies: C# .NET5, Angular, NodeJS, MSSQL, Laravel, MySQL, AWS, Bootstrap, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Software Design

Aug 2021 – Jan 2022

#### **Ginilab Limited**

Sunderland, England

Software Engineer

- Worked on Restaurant Management System.
- Added new features, and debugging.
- Technologies: .NET Framework, DevExpress, WinForms, Software Design, Fron-end, and Back-end.

#### Feb 2021 - Jul 2021

#### OurEdu

Dhaka, Bangladesh

Software Engineer

- Worked on Account Management System.
- Upgrading the old technology to new technology.
- Technologies: C# ASP.NET Core 3.1, JavaScript, Bootstrap, jQuery, LINQ, CSS, MSSQL, and DevOps.

## Jan 2015 – Jan 2021 Dhaka, Bangladesh

### Bangladesh Study Forum (BDSF)

Head of Information and Communication Technology ☑

- Developed the whole IT system for this organization.
- · Lead the IT team.
- What have I done: Website development, Organized programs, public speaking, Leadership.

## PROJECTS

#### Aug 2022 - present

#### Amedig Management 2

Warehouse Management

• Technologie: Azure DevOps, .NET Framework, MSSQL Server, Angular

#### Feb 2022 - Jul 2022

#### Bachao ra

Against the rape

- It's a mobile application platform against rape.
- The backend was developed with .NET.
- Technologies: .NET5, Angular, WebAPI, MSSQL

#### Aug 2021 - Jan 2022

## **Restaurant Management System**

- It's a desktop software, mostly used in the UK and in the middle east.
- Nearly 200+ restaurants and thousands of customers use this software for ordering food inside and outside the restaurant.
- Added new features and debugging.
- Technologies: ASP.NET, DevExpress, WinForms, MySQL, Laragon, HeidiSQL

#### Feb 2021 - May 2021

# Account Management System for Shidlai Ashraf Secondary School

- Enroll new students with details information.
- · Adding new staff and teachers.
- Payroll and tuition fees management.
- Online payment module.
- Technologies: C#, ASP.NET Core 3.1, JavaScript, Bootstrap, CSS, jQuery, JSON, LINQ, and following Onion Architecture.

#### May 2019 - Aug 2019

#### **Library Management System**

Technologies: C#, ASP.NET Core 2.1, Bootstrap, CSS, jQuery, JSON, LINQ.

# SKILLS

Frontend **Programming** VueJS, Angular, HTML5, Bootstrap, CSS3, Sass Language C, C++, Java, JavaScript, C#, R, Python, **Frameworks TypeScript** .NET Core. .NET. Laravel **Backend DevOps** NodeJS AWS, GCP, Azure, Docker, Jenkins, Kubernetes, Bash **Database** Oracle, MySQL, MSSQL Server, PostgreSQL Data Structure and • Source Control Algorithm Git, GitHub Cyber Security Interpersonal skills • Penetration, Forensics, Reverse Engineering,

Social Engineering

## **EDUCATION**

Responsibility, Teamwork

Listening, Caring, Leadership, Self-Motivated,

May 2021
Bachelor of Science in Computer Science and Engineering
International University of Business Agriculture and Technology
Completed BSc with a CGPA of 3.27 out of 4.00

Jul 2011 – Aug 2013
Higher Secondary Certificate
Cambrian College
Completed HSC with a GPA of 5.00 out of 5.00

Jan 2009 – May 2011
Secondary School Certificate
Cumilla, Bangladesh
Shidlai Ashraf Secondary School
Completed SSC with a GPA of 5.00 out of 5.00

# **♂** INTERESTS

- Learning New Skills
- Public Speaking
- Reading

Writing

Leadership

# LANGUAGES

Bangla • • • • English • • • •